[ {
    "id":"1",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Atoms with the same atomic number but different masses (same number of protons, but different number of neutrons)",
    "back": "isotopes"
},

{
    "id":"2",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Hybrid atomic orbitals that arise from the combination of one s orbital and two p orbitals",
    "back": "sp²"
},

{
    "id":"3",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Hybrid atomic orbitals that arise from the combination of one s orbital and three p orbitals",
    "back": "sp³"
},

{
    "id":"4",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Conceptually, combining atomic orbitals to obtain hybrid atomic orbitals in a way that facilitates the description of bonding within a molecule",
    "back": "hybridization"
},

{
    "id":"5",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "A bond formed by sideways overlap of atomic orbitals, resulting in electron density above and below a line between the two nuclei",
    "back": "pi bond (π bond)"
},

{
    "id":"6",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Valence electrons that are not involved in bonding",
    "back": "lone pair (non-bonding electrons)"
},

{
    "id":"7",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "The tendency for main group elements, eg. C, N, O, to attain eight electrons in their valence shells",
    "back": "octet rule"
},

{
    "id":"8",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Two atoms share a pair of electrons",
    "back": "covalent bond"
},

{
    "id":"9",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Arrangement of four groups around a central atom, with maximum distance between them (~ 109.5° bond angles)",
    "back": "tetrahedral"
},

{
    "id":"10",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "A single, unchanging structure which can be represented by multiple resonance structures (forms)",
    "back": "resonance hybrid"
},

{
    "id":"11",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "Alternate structure diagrams for a molecule which can be interconverted by shifting only π and non-bonding valence electrons",
    "back": "resonance structures (resonance forms)"
},

{
    "id":"12",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "In a structure diagram, the charge associated with an atom which does not possess the appropriate number of valence electrons",
    "back": "formal charge"
},

{
    "id":"13",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "A characteristic group of atoms and/or bonds that have predictable chemical behaviors",
    "back": "functional group"
},

{
    "id":"14",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "A structure diagram that avoids explicitly showing carbon atoms and hydrogen atoms that are attached to carbon",
    "back": "line-bond structure (bond-line structure)"
},

{
    "id":"15",
    "type":"1",
    "front": "A structure diagram that shows no bonds, instead implying bonds by clustering atoms and groups of atoms together",
    "back": "condensed structure"
}

]